(Sheldon:)Who is it?
(Sheldon:)Oh, hello, Penny. It's open. Come in.
(Sheldon:)Sarcasm.
- Well, they're all still up there.
- You think I can't hear them?
(Sheldon:)Listen to that. Stomp, stomp, stomp.
It's Wolowitz in his stacked heels
that fool no one.
(Penny:)I don't even know why I care.
I don't care.
(Penny:)All right, I cared enough to memorize
that stupid joke, but that's all I care.
(Sheldon:)You know, Penny...
(Sheldon:)...there's something that occurs in beehives
you might find interesting.
(Sheldon:)Occasionally, a new queen will arrive
while the old queen is still in power.
(Sheldon:)When this happens, the old queen
must either locate to a new hive...
(Sheldon:)...or engage in a battle to the death
until only one queen remains.
What are you saying?
That I'm threatened by Alicia?
(Penny:)That I'm like the old queen of the hive,
and it's just time for me to go?